trainings.push(
    {
        name: "HTML-Basis-Training",
        description: "",

        fragen: [
    {
        "antwort":  "<!--...-->",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines a comment"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<!DOCTYPE>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines the document type"
    },  
    {
        "antwort":  '<a href="http://www.google.de" target="_blank">Google this!</a>',
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Define a hyperlink to http://www.google.de that opens a new tab when clicked, and using the visible text of 'Google this!'!"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<abbr>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines an abbreviation or an acronym"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<address>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines contact information for the author/owner of a document"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<area>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines an area inside an image-map"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<article>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines an article"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<aside>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines content aside from the page content"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<audio>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines sound content"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<b>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines bold text"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<base>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Specifies the base URL/target for all relative URLs in a document"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<bdi>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Isolates a part of text that might be formatted in a different direction from other text outside it"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<bdo>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Overrides the current text direction"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<blockquote>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines a section that is quoted from another source"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<body>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines the document\u0027s body"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<br>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines a single line break"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<button>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines a clickable button"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<canvas>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Used to draw graphics, on the fly, via scripting (usually JavaScript)"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<caption>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines a table caption"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<cite>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines the title of a work"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<code>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines a piece of computer code"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<col>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Specifies column properties for each column within a <colgroup> element "
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<colgroup>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Specifies a group of one or more columns in a table for formatting"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<datalist>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Specifies a list of pre-defined options for input controls"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<dd>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines a description/value of a term in a description list"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<del>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines text that has been deleted from a document"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<details>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines additional details that the user can view or hide"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<dfn>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Represents the defining instance of a term"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<dialog>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines a dialog box or window"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<div>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines a section in a document"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<dl>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines a description list"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<dt>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines a term/name in a description list"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<em>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines emphasized text "
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<embed>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines a container for an external (non-HTML) application"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<fieldset>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Groups related elements in a form"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<figcaption>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines a caption for a <figure> element"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<figure>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Specifies self-contained content"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<footer>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines a footer for a document or section"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<form>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines an HTML form for user input"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<h1> to <h6>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines HTML headings"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<head>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines information about the document"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<header>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines a header for a document or section"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<hr>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines a thematic change in the content"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<html>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines the root of an HTML document"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<i>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines a part of text in an alternate voice or mood"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<iframe>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines an inline frame"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<img>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines an image"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<input>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines an input control"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<ins>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines a text that has been inserted into a document"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<kbd>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines keyboard input"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<keygen>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines a key-pair generator field (for forms)"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<label>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines a label for an <input> element"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<legend>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines a caption for a <fieldset> element"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<li>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines a list item"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<link>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines the relationship between a document and an external resource (most used to link to style sheets)"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<main>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Specifies the main content of a document"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<map>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines a client-side image-map"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<mark>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines marked/highlighted text"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<menu>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines a list/menu of commands"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<menuitem>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines a command/menu item that the user can invoke from a popup menu"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<meta>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines metadata about an HTML document"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<meter>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines a scalar measurement within a known range (a gauge)"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<nav>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines navigation links"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<noscript>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines an alternate content for users that do not support client-side scripts"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<object>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines an embedded object"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<ol>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines an ordered list"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<optgroup>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines a group of related options in a drop-down list"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<option>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines an option in a drop-down list"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<output>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines the result of a calculation"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<p>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines a paragraph"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<param>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines a parameter for an object"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<pre>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines preformatted text"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<progress>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Represents the progress of a task"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<q>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines a short quotation"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<rp>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines what to show in browsers that do not support ruby annotations"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<rt>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines an explanation/pronunciation of characters (for East Asian typography)"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<ruby>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines a ruby annotation (for East Asian typography)"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<s>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines text that is no longer correct"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<samp>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines sample output from a computer program"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<script>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines a client-side script"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<section>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines a section in a document"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<select>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines a drop-down list"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<small>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines smaller text"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<source>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines multiple media resources for media elements (<video> and <audio>)"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<span>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines a section in a document"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<strong>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines important text"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<style>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines style information for a document"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<sub>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines subscripted text"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<summary>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines a visible heading for a <details> element"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<sup>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines superscripted text"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<table>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines a table"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<tbody>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Groups the body content in a table"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<td>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines a cell in a table"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<textarea>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines a multiline input control (text area)"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<tfoot>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Groups the footer content in a table"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<th>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines a header cell in a table"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<thead>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Groups the header content in a table"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<time>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines a date/time"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<title>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines a title for the document"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<tr>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines a row in a table"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<track>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines text tracks for media elements (<video> and <audio>)"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<u>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines text that should be stylistically different from normal text"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<ul>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines an unordered list"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<var>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines a variable"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<video>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines a video or movie"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "<wbr>",
        "kategorie":  "HTML5-Elements",
        "frage":  "Defines a possible line-break"
    }
]});